Behold!
（猿投山(さなげやま)）見たか！
SUPER ULTIMA UNIFORM
HUNDRED-MAN ASSAULT
This is the Super Ultima Uniform Hundred-Man Assault!
これぞ超極(ごく)制服 百騎馬(ひゃっきば)戦陣
Charge!
突撃！
We're not done yet!
でや〜
It's a super high-speed jammer!
（伊織(いおり)）超高速邪魔浴(じゃまー)だ
細かい生命戦維(せんい)が高速回転して…
Millions of tiny Life Fibers are
...rotating at a very high speed—
Whoa! It's a huge rubber barrier!
（マコ）うわ〜
でっかいゴムのバリアーだよ
（猿投山）いってって…
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）猿投山！
Sanageyama!
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）また１人で先走るから
This is what you get for
barging in on your own.
（犬牟田(いぬむた)）
まったく学ばない男だね君は
You never learn, do you?
...Unless we take that jammer out...
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）
あの邪魔浴を止めなければ
（黄長瀬(きながせ)）
手も足も出せないってことか！
...we can't do a thing, huh?...
（皐月(さつき)）てやあ！
（羅暁(らぎょう)）フン！
（流子(りゅうこ)）おりゃ〜！
Hup!
（縫(ぬい)）はい！
（縫）はい！
You two always behave
in such an unsightly fashion.
（羅暁）
いつまでも目障りな… 今
Let me show you who's boss.
誰が主(あるじ)か教えてやろう
What the?
（犬牟田）これは？
（蛇崩）星がない！
The stars are gone!
Omnisilk Kouketsu:
Absolute Domination!
絶対服従
EPISODE 24
BEYOND THE INFINITE DARKNESS
ど… どうした鮮血(せんけつ)
What's wrong, Senketsu?
（鮮血）ダメだ 力が出ない
I've lost all my strength.
あの輝きに当たると
身がすくんでしまう
That light causes all who
touch it to cower in terror!
Omnisilk Kouketsu
rules over all Life Fibers.
（羅暁）神羅纐纈は
全ての生命戦維(せんい)の上に立つ
Any Life Fiber that opposes it
will tremble in fear and lose all power.
これに逆らう生命戦維は
恐れおののき無力化する
これが絶対服従だ
That is Absolute Domination.
ABSOLUTE DOMINATION
Here are the pictures our communications
satellite took from all over the world.
（羅暁）
通信衛星が捉えた全世界の映像だ
Just take a look.
見なさい 世界中の人々が
ＲＥＶＯＣＳ(リボックス)社製の服を着ている
Everyone across the globe is
clad in REVOCS, Inc. clothing.
Unleashing Absolute Domination
across the whole world
絶対服従の力を
全世界に放つことで—
will awaken the Life Fibers
lying dormant in those outfits.
ＲＥＶＯＣＳ社の服に眠る
生命戦維が覚醒
All of mankind will be
consumed by clothing,
全ての人類は服に取り込まれ
この地球は１枚の布に包まれる
and this planet will be covered
in a single piece of cloth.
Earth will become another
Celestial Seed Cocoon Planet,
地球は天種繭星(あまつだねのまゆぼし)となり—
新しく誕生した生命戦維が
また宇宙に広がっていく
and newborn Life Fibers shall
once again spread across the universe.
Wonderful.
すてき
（羅暁）これこそが宇宙の真理
That is the truth
behind the universe.
You have all been stripped
of the means to resist.
もう貴様たちに
あらがうすべはない
Don't forget about us!
（黄長瀬･美木杉）
まだ俺たちが—
We're still here!
残ってるぜ！
（黄長瀬）裸のヌーディスト魂
（美木杉）脱ぎ切る！
...And we'll show off...
our naked souls!
Ultimate Double Naked DTR!
ULTIMATE DOUBLE NAKED DTR
I don't think so.
（羅暁）問題外だ
Huh? You're not gonna kill them?
（縫）あれ？ 殺しちゃわないの？
（羅暁）まだだ
Not yet.
They're a valuable energy source
for the original Life Fiber.
（羅暁）
こやつらは原初(げんしょ)生命戦維の—
大切なエネルギー源だからな
（黄長瀬･美木杉）ぐわ〜
The original Life Fiber?
（鮮血）原初生命戦維が…
（流子）まだ生きてやがったのか
It's still alive?
The original Life Fiber will consume
you all and return in its full glory.
（羅暁）お前たちを飲み込んで
原初生命戦維はよみがえる
I'm sorry, Ryuuko,
すまない流子
お前が命を懸けた戦法も無駄にして
but the plan you risked
your life for was all in vain.
Not yet!
（蟇郡）まだだ！
俺たちは まだ終わっちゃいない！
We're not done yet!
（流子）蟇郡！ マコ！ みんな！
Gamagoori!
Mako!
Guys!
Oho?
あらあら 絶対服従の中で
動けるなんて大した怪力ね
You can move even under the influence of
Absolute Domination? You're impressively strong.
But it's futile.
でも無駄 人は所詮 服の奴隷
Humans are meant
to be slaves to clothing.
That hierarchy will never, ever change!
（縫）この関係は
永遠に変わらないの
（マコ）むう〜
（縫）この関係は
永遠に変わらないの
（マコ）う〜ん ぐわっ
That's not true!
そんなことない！
絶対そんなことないよ
It can't be true!
I mean, there's no hierarchy in the
relationship between Ryuuko and Senketsu!
だって流子ちゃんと
鮮血ちゃんの関係に
どっちが上か下かなんてないもん
それが服と人のいい関係だよ
That's what humans and clothing
are supposed to be like!
I've had enough of your shtick.
それ もう飽きたから
Die!
死んじゃえ！
G-Gamagoori!
せ… 先輩！
As Honnouji Academy's Disciplinary
Bureau Chairman, I, Gamagoori Ira,
本能字(ほんのうじ)学園 風紀部委員長
蟇郡苛(いら)
will protect Kiryuuin Satsuki
and all of Honnouji's students!
鬼龍院(きりゅういん)皐月と
本能字学園生徒を守る—
I am their living shield!
生きた盾と知れ！
Ugly, ugly, ugly!
醜い 醜い 醜い！ 醜い猿が！
You're one ugly primate!
Not on my watch!
させねえよ
You bitch...
（縫）貴様
（流子）神衣(かむい)は使えねえみたいだが
私だけならまだ戦える
You may have rendered
Godrobes powerless,
but I can still fight by myself.
体ん中の生命戦維のおかげでな！
It's all thanks to the
Life Fibers within my body.
What?
（縫）何？
I am neither human nor clothing.
（流子）
私は人でもなければ服でもない
どっちつかずの存在だ
Rather, I'm somewhere in between.
But right now,
I'm grateful to have this body.
だけど今は この体に
してくれたことに感謝してるぜ
Because it looks like I'm the only one immune
to that Absolute Domination crap of yours!
私だけには その絶対服従も
効かないみたいだからな！
Gamagoori!
先輩 蟇郡先輩！
So you're okay, Mankanshoku?
無事だったか 満艦飾(まんかんしょく)…
ならばよし
Then I regret nothing.
せ… 先輩！
G-Gamagoori!
Gamagoori!
蟇郡…
針目(はりめ) 貴様！
Harime, you bitch!
...You bastards...
てめえら
（羅暁）フハハハ…
（縫）アハハ…
Come, Ryuuko.
（羅暁）来い 流子
This is it.
（羅暁）ここだ
（縫）ここだって
Lookie here.
It's all thanks to Hououmaru here
that Absolute Domination is active.
（羅暁）
ここに眠る鳳凰丸(ほうおうまる)の力で—
Right here.
（縫）ここだよ
絶対服従は発動している
This is what you should be targeting.
狙うのはここだ
Don't look down on me!
（流子）なめるな！ うっ
But it's not like you can do anything,
even with that knowledge!
（羅暁）だが わかったところで
お前に手出しはできない
（流子）だあっ ううっ
（羅暁）だが わかったところで
お前に手出しはできない
流子 むちゃだ！
You're being reckless, Ryuuko!
Settle down, Senketsu!
（皐月）落ち着け鮮血
（鮮血）だ… だが流子が！
...But... But Ryuuko's...
I know how you feel.
お前の気持ちはわかる
However, Ryuuko won't stop
just because we tell her to.
だが私たちが言って
止まる流子ではない
...Satsuki! Can you...
皐月 お前 私の声が？
ああ聞こえる
Yeah. I can hear you.
I see.
（鮮血）そうか
Lady Ragyou.
（縫）羅暁様
（羅暁）うむ
It's almost time.
（羅暁）そろそろか
...Now...
（羅暁）
さあ これで人類は終わりだ
This marks the end for mankind.
Guys!
みんな！ あっ
I'll start with your friends.
（羅暁）まずは お前の仲間からだ
They'll all come together to form a single
piece of cloth that will cover this planet.
皆 地球を覆う１枚の布となる
H-How?
な… なぜ？
I, too, am neither human nor clothing.
人でも服でもないのは私も同じだ
Blade Gale!
疾風閃刃(せんじん)！
（羅暁）ぐわ〜！
...Is this...
（猿投山）これは…
（蛇崩）体が動く！
I can move again!
（犬牟田）
極制服の力が戻ったってことだね
This must mean our Ultima Uniforms
have regained their powers.
Precisely.
そのとおりだ
Life Fiber Override:
人衣(じんい)圧倒 神衣純潔
Godrobe Junketsu!
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
（一同）うや〜！
（一同）やあ〜！
Mankanshoku!
満艦飾君！
I never expected you to
be the one who'd save us.
まさか君に救われるとはね
No need to thank me.
礼はいらんですよ
Good job, Senketsu!
（流子）よくやった鮮血！
See that, Ragyou?
（皐月）見たか羅暁！
This is the power of those
so-called imitations of yours!
これが貴様が
まがい物と笑った者たちの力だ！
...Why? How could a fake Godrobe...
なぜだ？ 神衣もどきに…
It's because he's a fake.
“もどき”だからだ
I realized it when my voice
managed to reach Satsuki.
（鮮血）
私の声が皐月に届いたとき
気付いたのだ
That I'd been given the
same powers as Ryuuko!
私にも流子と同じ力が
与えられていると！
...We're neither humans...
（流子）人でもなければ…
（鮮血）服でもない
nor clothing!
...And that is the real...
（流子･鮮血）これがホントの—
Life Fiber Synchronize!
人衣一体だ！
Ryuuko!
（皐月）流子！
ぬうう
You guys take care of the transmitter.
（皐月）お前たちは発信装置を
（３人）はっ
Yes, ma'am!
（３人）とうっ
Nope.
（縫）ダメ！ ダメダメダメ〜
Nope, nope, nope!
You guys will have to go through me!
あなたたちの相手は私よ！
Mon mignon prêt-à-porter!
（縫）
モン ミニョン プレタポルテ！
Oh, shut up, you mass-produced rip-offs!
何 言ってんの
量産品のパチモンが！
ギャハハ…
（犬牟田）
フン！ データを取る価値もない
These aren't even worth
collecting data from.
ギャハハ〜
There's no end to them!
（猿投山）切りがない
（犬牟田）これじゃ装置に…
...We can't get to...
（蛇崩）近づけやしない！
...the transmitter!...
Leave the transmitter to me!
発信装置は俺に！
任せてもらおう！
Gamagoori! You're alive!
生きてたんですか？ 先輩！
Yeah.
I had a metalworker relative of mine fashion
this custom-made titanium protector just in case.
念のために親戚の鉄工所特製の
チタン鋼腹巻きを着けていた
It hurt a little, but it's
barely a flesh wound!
ちょっと痛かったが
大した傷じゃない
Quit trying to act cool!
You totally passed out there!
気絶してたくせに
かっこつけてんじゃないわよ！
I'll make up for that
disgrace with my actions!
（蟇郡）その醜態は行動で償う
Shackle Regalia:
縛(しばり)の装 我心(がしん)開放
Ego Burst!
SHACKLE REGALIA
EGO BURST
Behold the power of Ego Burst!
見よ！
この我心開放の力
It frees me of my restraints and
allows me to unleash my emotions!
いましめを解き おごりをなげうつ
食らえ！
Eat this!
UNRESTRAINED
EGO BLAST
Unrestrained Ego Blast!
縛解傲擲(ばくかいごうてき)
UNRESTRAINED
EGO BLAST
とやあ〜！
（黄長瀬）あとは任せろ！
Leave the rest to us!
Let us exhibit what we nudists can do!
ヌーディストのいいところも
少しは見せないと—
To do so, we need only expose ourselves!
ただの脱ぎ損だ！
You're just a plain exhibitionist!
（黄長瀬）あんたは
好きで脱いでるんだろうが！
（羅暁）何？
What?
（流子･皐月）うや〜！
（流子･皐月）だあ〜！
...No way...
そんな…
Your grand Cocoon Planet
Genesis plan is in tatters now,
（皐月）繭星(まゆぼし)降誕の野望も
ついえたな 羅暁！
Ragyou!
I wouldn't be so sure.
そうかな？
Nui!
縫！ その体 捨てろ
Cast away your body.
Oui, Maman!
ウイ ママ！
アハハ…
What the hell is that?!
何だ？ こりゃ
Nui, my girl.
（羅暁）縫よ
My pitiful girl who couldn't don Life Fibers because
the ones within her body were too powerful.
体内に宿した生命戦維が
強すぎるがゆえ—
生命戦維をまとうことが
できなかった哀れな娘よ
...But at last, you managed to wear...
だが最後に着ることができた
the greatest dress of all:
the original Life Fiber.
原初生命戦維という
最高のドレスをな
No, Lady Ragyou.
（縫）いいえ羅暁様
あなたが着るのです この僕を！
You will be the one to wear me!
Marvelous.
（羅暁）すばらしい
実にいい着心地だよ縫
You feel amazing to wear, Nui.
Of course I do.
当然でしょ でもうれしい
But that still makes me happy!
...Nui...
（羅暁）
縫 あとのことは任せなさい
Leave the rest to me.
ま… 待ちやがれ！
Hold it!
I figured out what
Ragyou's planning to do.
（犬牟田）
羅暁の狙いがわかりました
She's headed for REVOCS, Inc.'s
communications satellite!
（犬牟田）
彼女が向かってるのは
ＲＥＶＯＣＳ社の通信衛星です
So Ragyou and Kouketsu are gonna
make direct contact with the satellite
（美木杉）
羅暁と纐纈が直接衛星に接触し—
絶対服従の信号を
世界中に発信するってか
to transmit the Absolute Domination
signal across the world?
（皐月）
ああ だがこれは覚醒信号だから
我々の極制服を無効化できない
Yes.
But that's an activation signal.
It can't nullify our Ultima Uniforms.
We still have a chance!
反撃の手はある
...Now awaken...
（羅暁）さあ 目覚めよ
every last Life Fiber.
全ての生命戦維よ
Return to your original form,
本来の姿となり
and cover this entire planet!
この星を覆い尽くせ
Omnisilk Kouketsu:
神羅纐纈 絶対服従！
Absolute Domination!
（人々）うわ！
（人々）おわっ
So it's begun.
（皐月）始まったか
（流子）私が行く
（皐月）ん？
I'll go.
I'll go!
（流子）私が—
行く！
Let's go on a date, Ryuuko!
（マコ）流子ちゃん デートしよ！
（流子）は？
Listen up.
（マコ）聞いて！ 流子ちゃん
帰ってきたらデートしよう
Let's go on a date once you're back.
Let's dress up in cute clothes,
かわいい服着て
かわいいアクセサリー着けて
put on some cute accessories,
買い物したり
アイスクリーム食べたり
go shopping, and eat ice cream
in a world where girls are free
to dress up in the clothes they like!
女の子が好きな服 好きに着て
安心しておしゃれができる—
そんな世界に
流子ちゃんがしてくれる
I'm sure you'll create a world like that!
A world like that!
してくれる してくれる！
わかった！
Gotcha.
We're counting on you.
頼んだぞ 人類の生存のために…
...For mankind's surviva—
女の子のおしゃれのために！
For girls' fashion!
（流子）任せろ！
Leave it to me!
Allow me to wear
all of your Ultima Uniforms!
（流子）お前たちの極制服全部
私が着させてもらう！
Senketsu Fashion Week!
鮮血更衣(きさらぎ)
SENKETSU
FASHION
WEEK
Beautiful.
（羅暁）美しい
Truly beautiful.
実に美しい
This is the genesis of the Cocoon Planet.
これこそ繭星降誕
何？
What?
That's enough, Ragyou!
（流子）そこまでだ 羅暁！
（羅暁）なるほど
手持ちの生命戦維を—
I see.
So you stitched together all the
Life Fibers you had to get here.
パッチワークにして
ここまで来たか
But it's too late.
だが もう遅い
Look at the surface.
見ろ 地上を
世界中の生命戦維に信号は届いた
My signal made it to every
Life Fiber across the planet.
Mankind's fusion into clothing
can no longer be stopped.
もう全人類の布化(ぬのか)は止まらない
I can't just give up that easily.
（流子）
そう簡単には諦めらんねえんだよ
I've got a date riding on this!
こっちには—
デートがかかってんだ！
What nonsense.
たわ言を
（流子）食らえ！
（羅暁）アハハ… どうした？
What's the matter?
Those Sword Scissors are
essentially hardened Life Fibers too.
その断ち斬りバサミも
元は硬化生命戦維だ
They are powerless against my Absolute Domination,
which rules over all Life Fibers!
全ての生命戦維の上に立つ
絶対服従の前には無力なのだよ
（流子）そんな
No way!
Even so, you committed the grave sin of
pointing your blade at this divine garment.
だが この神にも等しき
偉大なる衣に刃(やいば)を向けた罪は…
For that, you will pay!
（羅暁）
あがなわなければならない！
Pull yourself together, Ryuuko!
（鮮血）流子 しっかりしろ！
Yeah, I'm fine!
（流子）
ああ大丈夫だ まだいける！
I can still fight!
Oh, you poor girl. You've been
shackled by Souichirou's will.
（羅暁）装一郎(そういちろう)の意志に
縛りつけられた哀れな娘よ
Why can't you comprehend the truth
behind the universe when you're that powerful?
それだけの力がありながら
なぜ宇宙の真理がわからぬ！
Take a look, Ryuuko.
見ろ流子 あの青き星を
At that blue planet.
At the shining sun.
輝く太陽を 瞬く星々を
これが宇宙だ
At those twinkling stars.
This is space.
But even this beautiful sight
will one day be gone.
だが この美しき光景もやがて滅ぶ
創生と消滅
All creations will ultimately perish.
That was determined the
moment this universe was born.
それはこの銀河が誕生したときから
決定づけられたことだ
The actions of the Life Fibers are
merely in accordance with that principle.
生命戦維の営みも同様だ
宇宙の真理の一部なのだよ
They are but one part of
the truth behind the universe!
Enough of your prattle!
（流子）能書きはそこまでだ！
You're my daughter!
我が娘ながら
なぜそう物わかりが悪い！
How can you be so dull?!
I wasn't raised by you!
てめえに育てられたわけじゃねえ！
そうか それは失敬したな！
Oh, I see.
How rude of me!
That's not nearly enough to kill me off!
（流子）その程度じゃ
私に引導は渡せねえ！
Hmm. I must have unwittingly held back.
ふむ 無意識に手心を加えたか
It seems I still harbor the
faintest trace of a human heart.
私にも少しは人の心が
残っていたようだな
In that case,
ならば 人の心 捨てようか！
I should cast it aside!
This is the end!
これで終わりだ！
I'll be the one to decide my end.
私の終わりは私が決める
てめえに指図は受けねえぜ！
You're not the boss of me!
Are you regenerating faster now?
（羅暁）回復のスピードが
上がっているのか
その生命戦維との親和力の高さ
惜しいことだよ！
It's a shame that I have to kill someone
who has so high an affinity with Life Fibers!
In that case, you could
go a little easier on me!
惜しいんなら少しは容赦しろ！
Ryuuko, we're running out of time!
（鮮血）
流子マズいぞ 時間がない！
（流子）わかった
All right.
I'll end this now!
これで決める！
（羅暁）ハハハ…
何を決めるというのだ？
End what, exactly?
Your own life?
己の最期か？
（流子）うっ…
終わるのはお前のほうだ
No, yours.
What?
何？
（流子）忘れたのか？
Did you forget already?
The closer I come to death,
the more powerful I become!
私は死にかければ死にかけるほど
強くなってよみがえる
What? Don't tell me you
took that attack on purpose!
お前 まさかわざと私の攻撃を…
Sure did.
ああ 母の愛のムチだと思って
しっかり食らわせてもらったよ
I thought of it as my mother's
tough love, and I took it on the chin.
So that Senketsu and I could
reach the peak of our strength!
私と鮮血が最高に成長するまで！
It matters not!
Life Fibers cannot harm me!
（羅暁）だが生命戦維が
私を傷つけることはできない
Even if I take that
Absolute Domination ability for myself?
（流子）
その絶対服従の力 頂いてもか！
...You can't mean...
まさか
The Sword Scissors weren't
Dad's final weapon.
（流子）父さんの最後の武器は
断ち斬りバサミなんかじゃねえ！
It was Senketsu and me!
私と鮮血だったんだ！
Say what?
何！
It's the unlimited absorption ability
that the two of us possess!
（流子）
２人に備わった無限の吸収能力だ！
（鮮血）神羅纐纈との
戦いの中で気付いたよ
I realized it during the fight
with Omnisilk Kouketsu.
The reason I've been absorbing Life Fibers
all this time was to hone that ability!
私が生命戦維を
吸収し続けてきたのも—
この力を育てるためだった
I was born capable of evolution.
私は進化する
自分の意志を持ち この言葉を
人間に伝えることが可能になる
And one day, I developed
a will of my own,
and was able to convey
my thoughts to people!
Yeah, we're neither humans nor clothing!
確かに私たちは
人でもなければ—
NOT HUMAN
服でもない
NOT CL OTHING
But at the same time,
（鮮血）
だが同時に私たちは—
we are humans, clothing,
人であり 服であり
全てであり
ARE HUMAN
ARE CLOTHING
and everything else!
ARE EVERYTHING
Humans can't become clothing!
（流子）人は服にはなれねえ！
Humans are humans,
ARE
HUMANS
人は人 服は服だ！
and clothing is clothing!
CLOT HING
IS
What is this incomprehensible garbage?!
（羅暁）何を訳の
わからないことを—
INCOMPREHENSIBLE
言っている！
That's just who we are!
THAT'S
US
（流子）
それが私たちってことだよ！
THAT'S
US
Hear my call, Life Fibers!
聞け！
全ての生命戦維よ
Humans are humans,
人は人 服は服だ！
and clothing is clothing!
Return all of mankind to
the humans they once were!
全ての人間を人間に戻せ！
She did it.
（揃(そろい)）やりましたね
（皐月）ああ
Yeah.
Now we're finally free
of the Kiryuuin family curse.
これで開放される
鬼龍院の宿業から
Impossible.
（羅暁）
バカな… こんなことが…
How could this be?
Will everything I strove
for come to naught?
全ては無に帰るというのか
That's right, Mom.
そういうことだよ 母さん
Earth won't ever become
a Cocoon Planet.
（流子）
もう地球が繭星になることはない
おとなしく地球に帰ろう
Surrender peacefully,
and let's go back together.
Ridiculous.
くだらんな
I'll be the one to decide my end.
己の最後は己が決める
Looks like I'll follow through
on those words before you do.
お前の言葉
私が先に果たさせてもらおう
Don't!
やめろ！
This is not the end, Ryuuko.
流子 これで終わりではないぞ
Life Fibers are still spreading
across the universe.
生命戦維は宇宙に広がり続けている
またこの星にもやって来る 必ずな
And they will reach
this planet again someday.
You can count on that.
Even so, humans will stay human.
それでも人は人であり続けるさ
必ずね
You can count on that.
フン！
Let's go back, Ryuuko.
（鮮血）帰るぞ 流子
What's the matter, Senketsu?
どうした鮮血
Looks like Omnisilk Kouketsu
was more powerful than I thought.
（鮮血）思ったよりも
神羅纐纈の力は大きかったようだ
...Don't tell me you're—
まさか お前
（鮮血）急ぐぞ 時間がない！
（流子）うわ〜
Let's hurry back.
We're running out of time!
Don't push yourself, Senketsu!
（流子）鮮血 無理するな！
It's a bit late to be saying that
after all we've been through.
（鮮血）
さんざん無理させてきたお前が
何を言う
（流子）鮮血！
（鮮血）だが これでいい
Senketsu!
But this is for the best.
I'm sure your father
can rest in peace now.
（鮮血）きっとお前の父さんも
満足しているだろう
I'm glad I met you.
楽しかったぞ お前に会えて
It was fun.
You idiot! I don't want your farewells!
（流子）バカ！
勝手にまとめるんじゃねえ！
Don't cry, Ryuuko.
（鮮血）泣くな流子
Sailor uniforms are
made to be grown out of.
セーラー服とは卒業するものだ
これからは好きな服を着ろ
From now on, you're
free to wear what you like.
Clothes that are far cuter
than I could ever be.
私よりも かわいい服をな
Fine! I'll do just that!
（流子）わかった 着てやるよ
お前が嫉妬するような服をな
I'll wear clothes that'll
dye you green with envy!
Senketsu!
鮮血！
...in there!...
（皐月）しっかりしろ…
しっかりしろ！
Hang in there!
Ryuuko!
（皐月）流子！
（流子）ハッ
（皐月）だああ〜！
Ryuuko!
流子！
流子ちゃん！ 流子ちゃ〜ん！
Ryuuko!
Matoi!
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）流子ちゃん！
（好代(すくよ)）流子ちゃん！
Ryuuko!
（又郎(またろう)）姉御！
（ガッツ）ガッツ〜！
Boss!
Guts!
Welcome back.
おかえり
I'm home, Sis.
ただいま 姉さん
What'll happen to the
rest of the Life Fibers?
（黄長瀬）
残った生命戦維はどうなる？
（美木杉）布型カバーズと同じだ
一旦 人体との融合を解いたら—
The same thing that
happened to COVERS, I guess.
Once they're separated
from the human body,
they'll be cut off from their
energy source and will perish naturally.
エネルギーを得ることができずに
自然消滅するだろうね
With this, Nudist Beach
has completed its mission.
これでヌーディスト･ビーチの
役目も完了だ
We can finally wear clothes again.
やっと服が着れるか
Now, then.
（美木杉）
さて 後始末が大変だが—
Cleaning up this mess
is going to be hard.
But it's our job as adults
to take care of it.
ここからが大人の仕事だ
Besides, those girls have a date to go on.
彼女たちにはデートがあるしね
katakuna ni itsumo
You're always so obstinate
yuzurou to shinai ne
Never willing to give in
otonagenai pride
Holding on to that childish pride of yours
douse minna sou
Everyone's the same
jibun ga kawaii
They put themselves first
mou iikagen ni shite
I've had enough of it all
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku wa michi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you